- It's some guy called Prasad.
- The driver?
- Which bike? Platina?
- Splendor. 8876.
Oh, that Prasad!
He lives right there.
There he is!
Right there!
Hey, stop!
Stop!
Catch him!
Follow him.
Sir.
Come on!
- Catch him!
Hey!
Let's go.
F****r!
Oye! Stop, you bloody...
"Mumbai city never slows down"
"Doesn't listen to nobody,
never hears a sound"
"Just tryin to survive here,
homie turned outlaw"
Fish for sale!
Moron! Trying to act smart.
You do this to me!
You ruined all my fish.
- What are you doing, lady!
Bloody idiot!
All my stock is gone!
Hey, stop!
Still want to run, rascal?
If you're innocent,
why'd you run?
You know how...
You pass a temple, you pray.
You see the police, you run.
Anyone will do it...
- Trying to act smart, motherf****r?
Look at this photo.
Who's that?
It's you, right?
Isn't it you riding pillion?
Tell me!
The guy's wearing a mask,
How would I recognize him?
Don't be a wise-a**!
Have some shame, d***head.
You're wearing
the same shirt.
Look at this!
- See!
Lying to our faces!
Now you're done for.
Intimidating a court witness,
motherf****r?
Making acid attack threats?
I'll pour acid where
it'll hurt you in a way,
that you will stop shitting!
Quick!
Speak!
Ok, ok...
It's not my fault, sir.
Then?
Everything...
They forced me.
I said I don't do such stuff.
They forced me to take the money,
and said nothing will happen.
"No one will find out."
"It's just water, not acid.
No one gets hurt."
I'm an idiot, sir!
Slap me! I deserve it. - Stop...
He...
Who is 'they'?
Who?
"Come on, baby!"
"Who you gonna pick tonight?"
"You, baby!"
"Come on, baby!"
"Who you gonna slay tonight?"
"You, baby!"
"Your heart and mine,
when they collide"
"It's love at first sight"
"Throw me a look,
don't be shy"
"Wanna make you mine"
"Your style, your fire,
got me reeling"
"You got me, baby!"
"We're young and wild,
time's on our side"
Oh, my love!
"Come on, baby!"
"Who you gonna pick tonight?"
"Who you gonna slay tonight?"
"Come on, baby!"
"Who you gonna pick tonight?"
If you perform like this
at a Delhi wedding,
no one is going to watch it!
If I wanted sad songs, I'd call
Jagjit Singh with his harmonium!
- He's dead.
- Who?
This way, Sunny ma'am!
How are you doing?
- I'm great, how are you?
- Fantastic.
Daniel sir, look here!
- Sir, will you have dinner?
- I'm not hungry.
I'm home.
Where are you?
Hi! We're out for that gig
I told you about.
Were you and I
supposed to meet tonight?
Either way, come if you can.
Everyone's asking about you.
It'll be nice.
Who are you with?
'You don't know them.'
Don't they...
They have names, right?
'Push harder, Syam...'
'Push harder!'
'Yeah, like that.'
Sorry, I forgot to
give you this earlier.
Shiva!
What's this nonsense?
Who gave it to you?
Sir, it's a notice
for the mortgage.
The bank officials said
this is the final one.
Failure to pay would mean...
Let me see.
- Shiva?
- Yes sir.
How many months' salary
do I owe you?
- Don't worry sir, I'll manage.
- Tell me, how many months?
It's... four months.
Here's two month's pay.
- No sir, I...
- Keep it.
I'll pay the rest next month.
- Hi!
I was just waiting for you.
I'm very hungry.
Can we order quickly, please?
Yeah, sure.
So, how's your back?
Not good.
Saw a doctor?
No point.
All he does
is to suggest surgery.
So?
My insurance has expired.
Can't you ask your parents?
Don't want to ask them anything.
What's the problem?
You're their son.
They're retired.
Don't want to worry them.
Then why don't you
do something about it?
You got all those TV offers.
It's good money.
I don't want to do TV.
TV is stupid.
Prashant has finished
a third draft,
and it's turned out really good,
you know? A solo starrer...
- Imagine...
- Do you hear yourself speak?
Didn't you say
you've been trying to make a film
for five years. It's not happening.
What if it never happens?
Get out of your bubble.
Even if he completes the script,
who'll produce it?
You don't have money
for your surgery!
How will you fund the film?
You got home pretty late
last night, right?
What?
What are you talking about?
You met someone.
Someone younger...
Someone richer.
Are we really talking
about this right now?
His name's Kabir, right?
Wow!
So you're stalking me now.
I'm not f*****g stalking you.
You were all over him
in all the photographs.
Do you, by some minute chance,
understand the concept of friendship?
Or is it too much
for your archaic brain?
Idiot!
Hey...
I'm sorry.
I overreacted.
Answer the phone.
Please?
Shiva!
Samir Mehra?
Samar Mehra.
Who are you? What happened?
Goddamnit!
Did you misspell the name?
I didn't do anything.
- You always screw up.
- Wait, I'll check.
- Excuse me?
- Shut up.
Sir, Papa Jacob here.
We're at the address.
The WhatsApp message says 'Samir',
but a Samar lives here.
Okay, sir.
It's just a typo.
Autocorrect glitch.
- But what's the name?
- Samar.
Right.
- Saamar Mehra?
- Samar Mehra.
Like "summer season"!
Got it.
Come on. You've been summoned
to the police station.
Police station?
Which station?
- There's a FIR against you.
- FIR?
I've done nothing.
What is this for?
Show him the warrant.
Warrant.
Here. Look.
Read this.
This is in Marathi,
I don't know the language.
Learn it then.
All our official documents
are in Marathi.
This is Maharashtra, after all!
Sa-ma-r.
Try it.
You'll learn it.
It's very simple.
You're definitely mistaken.
There's a Samir Mehra in B-wing.
Think we're fools?
Just a minute...
- Shut up and listen!
- Papa, one sec.
You have been summoned.
Autocorrect changed your name.
I've done nothing...
Hold on, speak to sir.
Sir, talk to him.
'Mehra motherf****r, come to
the police station right now...'
'Else they'll drag
your prettya**here!'
Why are you abusing?
Who are you?
'Want a bullet up your ass?
Come here right away!'
Satisfied?
Let's go in peace now.
Come.
But I've done nothing.
Yeah, everyone says that.
Get moving now. Let's go.
Okay, okay.
Let me get my phone
and wallet.
Carry your wallet for sure.
Full.
Only cash.
Wow! Look at his old photos.
Looked like a real hero, huh?
And now? He's become a villain.
- Sir, what happened?
- Call Khushi.
Yes, sir.
- You work for him?
- Yes.
- What's that?
- It's for sir.
For sir, eh?
I've watched your song
many times.
It's fantastic.
- Which one?
- This one.
My wife's a big fan
of your TV show.
The one with the little girl?
That one.
It's amazing.
Who filed a case against me?
Didn't I tell you?
You'll find out at the police station.
But what are the charges?
You don't know
what you've done?
Your crime is singing.
What's that vulgar song?
"Come on, baby!
Get laid tonight?" Right?
"Wanna get laid tonight."
Such filth!
It's 'Who'll you slay tonight?'
You should sing clearly then.
Loud and clear: 'Slay'!
If you slay,
it's Section 302.
Hey, Malti!
Look who's here.
'It's too dark, I can't see.'
Turn on the flashlight.
There you go.
Now can you see?
What are you doing?
'Who's that?'
Look there...
Come on, wave at her!
She's a fan.
'Who the hell is this?'
'I'm busy, stop bothering me.'
What's keeping you busy?
You spend all day gossiping
and watching reels.
- 'Wait till you get home!'
- Stop this nonsense!
He's a celebrity!
A bloody has-been.
Saamar Mehra...
one-hit wonder!
Inspector Deore's case.
Okay.
Write your name, number
and address here.
Hey, listen.
Show your government ID.
Government ID?
Remember the ID number?
Write that down.
Always keep it on your person.
- Hand over your phone.
- Give it here.
Give the mobile.
Out with it.
Take his photo
for the record.
Please can you tell me
what I've done?
You know a woman
named Gayatri, right?
She's filed a case
against you.
Section 376. Rape.
Rape. Assault. Understand?
Now give me your wallet.
Take his wallet
and check what's inside.
Wallet! Hurry up!
Hurry up!
Take his picture.
I want a lawyer.
Please give me my phone.
One minute.
I'm not authorised
to give you anything.
Just take his photo now,
don't waste time.
Fancypants wants a lawyer.
Trying to act smart!
Hand over your protein.
Peanuts?
These guys like it dirty.
Need some action?
Why did you rape her?
Looks like a real stud.
Get up. Come on.
Sign this.
What's this?
Declaration statement.
It says we got you here safely,
and with your consent.
I didn't come here willingly.
And I can't read this.
I won't sign it.
Just sign it!
I don't understand Marathi.
I need to speak to my lawyer.
Give me my phone.
What do you mean,
you moron?
Are you calling us liars?
I won't sign.
This is illegal!
You bloody...
I want my lawyer.
I won't sign anything until...
Look at this guy, sir.
He's refusing to sign.
Step back.
What's up, Samir?
Samar, not Samir!
Same thing.
Why won't you sign?
These documents are in Marathi.
I won't sign anything
until I speak to my lawyer.
Just do it tomorrow.
- Simple, right?
- Yes, sir.
Look.
It's a declaration,
not a confession. Relax.
Just sign it.
How do I know for sure?
I don't understand Marathi.
Don't you get it?
Jacob, bring him in.
Let's go.
Now you're screwed.
Sit.
Why won't you sign?
Sir, it's in Marathi,
I can't read what it says.
I've done nothing wrong.
That girl is a liar.
She's framing me...
She wants revenge.
Revenge for what?
You must've done something
for her to seek revenge.
She's a stalker, sir.
She would message me incessantly.
I blocked her.
You can check my phone.
She's blocked.
You blocked her? Sure?
Swear on your mother.
- Swear that you blocked her.
- I swear on my mother.
You swore on your mom,
now let Daddy show you something.
"Hey, baby..."
"What are you doing?"
Baby says:
"Just took a bath."
"Wow!"
Sir...
"Wish I could see you now..."
"In your towel."
"I'm not wearing any towel."
Sir...
"Oh!"
"I'm f*****g hard."
Your d**k goes up.
"Send me another..."
But sir...
"No", she says.
No means no.
Sir, I can explain...
Amitabh Bachchan says
"No means no". Right?
"Ok, here's something
from my side."
She didn't ask for anything.
And what did you send?
Your willy!
Recognise this dIIk?
It's yours, right?
It's not what it looks like.
What do you think, f****r?
Is this an awards show?
Are you here to shake your booty?
Sir...
If you're innocent,
what's this, a*****e?
Sir, I'm being polite.
Be respectful. Don't abuse!
Who's abusing, motherf****r?
Who motherf*****g
abused anyone?
Did I abuse?
You just said, mother-
What, 'motherf****r'?
Come on! That's not abuse.
See,
In grammar, we use this thing.
It's like, a line and a dot.
What do you call it in English...
"Exclamation mark".
When you see something
crazy or exciting,
you say:
"Motherf****r! What a place!"
"So much motherf*****g traffic!"
"I'm sweating like a motherf*****g pig!"
Don't you say shit like that?
Motherf****r is just motherf****r.
Dot-dot-dot. Motherf****r.
If I call you a mother-f****r,
does that make you one?
That girl called you a rapist.
Are you a rapist?
No, sir.
No, right?
Where did you meet her?
On a shoot?
On a dating app, sir.
'Dating'? Like a calendar?
- No, sir.
- Then?
Then?
Men and women who want to meet
can do so through the app.
Explain it to me.
How does it work?
People make profiles
and upload their photos.
If you like her photos,
you swipe right.
Otherwise you swipe left.
Do you pay for this?
No, sir.
So it's free?
You get girls for free?
You don't 'get' girls, sir.
If she's interested,
she swipes right.
Or else she swipes left.
If you want to do this
"left-right-left" nonsense,
Why not join the army,
serve the nation?
Sir, my father was in the army.
He was a Brigadier.
- Did he swipe left-right-left?
- Don't insult my father!
"Don't insult, don't abuse..."
Why are you
so damn sensitive?
What's offending you?
Explain it to me.
Sir, I'm just requesting you
to ask nicely...
I've been cooperating,
haven't I?
Ok, let's be respectful.
Be nice, motherf****rs.
A big star has graced us
with his presence!
We'll talk respectfully now.
My dear sir, you...
How do you say
'c**k' respectfully?
Ph****s.
So, your noble Ph****s
entered the girl's...
V****a.
You forced your noble Ph****s
into the girl's V****a.
What the fuck, sir?
Sir! He said 'fuck'!
The disrespect!
Why did you say 'fuck'?
You act all virtuous,
then say 'fuck' to us?
Sir, I got angry.
I'm sorry...
You can get angry,
and we can't, motherf****r?
You think we're f*****g morons?
I want to talk to my lawyer.
Give me my phone.
What grade is your lawyer?
5 zeroes? 4 zeroes? 3?
Or the ambulance chasers
hanging outside the court?
What's his grade?
Sir, please.
Feel free to use my phone.
I want to hear you
talk to this lawyer.
I didn't do it sir.
That girl is a liar!
I'm innocent.
Sir, please let me
talk to my lawyer.
Please give me my phone.
Your phone is not happening.
And I can do as I please.
My station, my rules.
Papa!
Go hydrate yourself.
Close it.
Let's read further.
"Why don't you pick my calls?"
"I'm busy, man."
"Yeah, I can clearly see that."
"Hey, listen,
I'm in some emergency..."
"When can I get the money?"
You write:
She says: "I told you
I need some time."
Why did you ask her for money?
- Sir, she had my money.
- What?
- My money was with her.
- Your money?
Yes, that's what
I needed from her.
Your money?
Yes!
You ask her for nudes,
then you blackmail her...
Motherf****r!
And you claim it's your money?
How much did you have?
Sir, I gave her my cash
during demonetisation...
She said she could
get the currency exchanged.
And?
She took the money
and never returned it.
Look...
You're charged under Section 376.
Rape. Blackmail. Extortion.
All three.
It's the Unholy Trinity!
The apocalypse is upon you.
If any judge sees
this d**k pic of yours,
you'll be jailed
for a decade at least.
I'll make sure of that.
You'll be stripped naked
in public. You know how?
I'll take this picture
of your willy,
and show it to everyone
on live TV.
How about that?
Don't cry, man.
Don't cry.
We're the police,
we're here to help.
Don't worry.
What's the best
you can do?
Twenty lakhs?
Just twenty lakhs!
What do you mean?
Do I have to spell it out?
Are you that thick?
Invest in us
instead of a lawyer.
We'll make a
conviction-proof chargesheet.
You'll get bail easily.
I don't have that kind of money.
Aww... "I have no money..."
You think we're idiots?
I'm asking nicely,
for the last time.
Arrange the money,
and your willy
stays in your pants.
Case dismissed.
Please understand.
His name is Samar Mehra.
He's been brought here
in the dead of the night.
I need to see him.
I know, but we
can't allow it now.
Come in the morning.
Why not?
And why is he here?
Bring him.
Tell me the charges.
I know my rights!
Khushi!
Why have they brought you here?
Come tomorrow morning, ma'am.
Khushi, call my sister.
She knows someone!
Are you listening to me?
Call my sister!
I am Samar Mehra's friend, sir.
What?
Can you tell me why
he's been brought here? Please!
Tell her why you're here.
Tell her, hero!
He's been charged with rape.
Okay?
If you still want to meet him,
come in the morning.
He sends d**k pics...
What nonsense-
You bloody-
Sir, sir, sir!
Sir, please don't.
I'll leave.
Please don't hit him.
Take her away.
Shiva, let's go.
Sir, can I give him
his medicines?
He has a condition...
Sure, ahead, doc!
Sorry, sir! Sorry, sir!
Settle down, guys.
Sit.
Lost another chair to anger.
Look at the filth
in his search history.
What does it say?
Too complicated for my brain.
You try?
Hey, give it to her to read.
Hemangi, you tell us.
You're an educated woman.
"Submissive Teenage Baby
with Dom Daddy."
What?
"Submissive Teenage Baby
with Dom Daddy."
Dom? What the hell is Dom?
Like 'Dormitory'?
Dome!
Dominant.
Dominant!
Where is Papa?
Jacob!
Come here quick.
Take the old man to Andheri.
Old man?
This old man here.
Flirty at fifty!
f*****g around with
women half his age.
Drop him to Andheri Jail.
He'll have his hearing tomorrow.
Andheri?
Don't act all soft.
It's an order.
Go, drag him out.
''19th of Trump.'
'The Sun.'
You're going to nail it.
The world may not see
right now,
But they will.
Good days are ahead.
Relax, it's ok.
Your blood pressure is low.
Sugar's low as well.
Do you take any medications for it?
It's better if we keep him
under observation for 24 hours.
Not possible, madam.
He has to be in court tomorrow.
Oh!
- What are the charges?
- Section 376.
Thanks to his blood sugar,
we get to enjoy ice-cream!
Nice?
Find a gap, take a nap.
Get some sleep.
Give me an ice cream, too.
Take your time.
Madam, I've already told you...
He's been shifted to another place.
Is there no process here?
You kept him all night,
without informing anyone.
Who's in charge here?
- Where did you shift him?
- Andheri jail.
Andheri jail?
Samar. What happened?
Suhani...
- Madam, please wait outside.
- Why are you looking like this?
Calm down.
I didn't do anything.
They're treating me really badly...
Did they hit you?
They took my phone...
Suhani, come here.
Please sit down.
We're in a Police station.
We have to cooperate.
Calm down.
I'll talk to them. Ok?
I'm Samar Mehra's lawyer,
Nitin Mukherjee.
I want an FIR copy.
Yes... of course.
Can you make it quick?
- Hurry, please.
- Sure.
Please do it fast.
You haven't told
Mom and Dad, right?
Where's Khushi?
She didn't come?
No. She called last night
to inform me.
Who's this Gayatri, brother?
Why is she doing this?
Did Khushi sound angry
on the phone?
I don't know. Who's Gayatri?
You spoke to her,
and you don't know?
I don't know, brother.
I don't f*****g care!
I'm f*****g stressed about you!
I don't care what Khushi feels,
what she's doing. I don't know.
Ok, Ok. I'm sorry.
Suhani, calm down.
Gather yourself together.
Did you say anything to the cops?
Made any confession?
Confession?
Why would I confess
when I've done nothing?
I've done nothing.
Did they give you
a settlement offer?
Yes.
Twenty lakhs.
We can negotiate
and try to bring it down...
I'm not negotiating.
I don't want to negotiate.
I don't have the money
to negotiate.
I can ask Papa.
I can help too...
No, you're not
going to ask them.
Listen to me.
I have done nothing.
I've not raped anybody.
I'm innocent.
- Did you have sex?
- You don't believe me?
Did you have sex?
Did you have sex
with her?
- Did you?
- Yes, I did.
Only once.
Because she insisted.
It was like
f*****g a dead body.
That's so inappropriate!
But that's the fact, Suhani.
And I did not sleep with her
after that.
Where did you meet her
for the first time?
Calm down.
- Where did you meet her?
- On a dating app.
- Who approached first?
- I did.
I was new to the app.
I thought right-swipe
meant rejecting someone.
Why did you
keep talking to her?
They've submitted
your entire message exchange.
And all this must be
post the sex, right?
Then why didn't you
block her?
Why didn't you tell her
you don't want to meet?
She knew where I live.
- Couldn't you lock your doors?
- Yes, but I couldn't stop her.
You know I can't say no.
Why not?
What did she do for you?
Cook your meals?
Clean your house?
I never asked her
for anything.
She would just come
and do things on her own.
And yes, I did block her.
I blocked her!
Did you ghost her?
Yes, I did.
What?
And how long did you ghost her,
before you blocked her?
After a very long time.
Did you meet Khushi
on the same dating app?
Yes.
But don't bring her
into this.
- Get the car ready for court.
- Yes, sir.
Can you get me out of here?
What do you think,
what are our chances?
Listen, you-
Is there?
Is there anything else
you'd like to tell me, because...
I have told you-
Try to understand,
I need to know everything.
Like, everything.
Whatever little information,
I need every detail.
I have nothing more to say.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, I am sure.
Hi, good morning.
Thanks for coming
at such short notice.
You're welcome.
Just go through this once.
Especially page 3.
And translate it for me.
Which part?
Mainly this, but just go through
the whole thing once.
I don't know what
f*****g bubble he lives in!
You know, I took the first flight
out of Kolkata.
Haven't slept all night.
I didn't come to see you
crying like this.
Come on.
Just fix yourself, ok?
We'll get this.
We'll be fine.
Just read it out to me.
My phone?
It's logged as evidence.
We can't give it back.
Here, wear this.
- I'm claustrophobic.
- What?
- I feel suffocated.
- This is a high profile case.
The media's waiting outside.
The more it blows up,
the harder it is to get bail.
Now wear this.
But...
Come on.
Let's go.
Careful.
'Do you like
to get choked?'
'Choke, as in?'
'As in...'
'I'll grab your throat,
hold you down...'
'And fuck your brains out.'
'Would you like that?'
Will you really choke me?
Take this off.
Let's go.
- Let's go.
- Hold on!
Come on.
Bhai...
They will not let you in.
Her lawyer filed an application saying
she might feel intimidated by you.
Sorry... I'm so sorry.
Couldn't come earlier.
I really should have.
- I'm sorry, baby.
- It's ok.
Bhai, we're going up.
Why didn't you tell me
about her?
I don't know.
I didn't think
it was important.
You grill me all the time
about every friend I ever meet!
You didn't think
this was important?
Khushi...
She doesn't mean
a thing to me.
I only slept with her once.
And that too before I met you.
Then why is she doing this?
I don't know.
Hi, Khushi.
We spoke on the phone.
Suhani.
- What happened?
- Sir.
She's his sister.
Can they speak in private?
Five minutes, please?
Thank you.
What happened?
She did the interiors
of your house?
Who?
The victim.
I'm the victim, not her.
She's a liar, Suhani.
She's a liar!
Listen.
Listen! Legally speaking,
just get this straight,
She's the victim,
and you are guilty...
until proven innocent.
So please,
just answer the question.
Go ahead, ask him.
Did she do the interiors
of your house or not?
No clue!
She would keep
fiddling around,
but everything in there
belongs to me.
But what did she do?
I don't know.
I was barely home.
Shiva was there.
The only thing I saw
was incense lying there.
You know what I saw inside?
I saw evidence.
She produced a bill to prove
she did your house interiors.
What is it called?
Feng Shui.
She kept saying...
That the 'energy'
in my house was wrong.
And she has to do
something about it.
He knows about it, see?
Why didn't you tell me this?
Why didn't he tell-
How would I know
this was important?
What did I say to you?
Tell me every little detail.
Didn't I?
You didn't tell me that she
worked on your house for a month!
A month?
She gave you crystals
worth 15 lakhs?
15 lakhs?
- The ones that lie by your bedside?
- I didn't know they were 15 lakhs!
That's not the point. Why didn't you
tell me the goddamn information?
He didn't tell me
anything either.
I asked. You said
it's for good energy!
And when I asked if you
believe in all of this,
you said it's my sister,
she believes in it!
I... I do.
Bhai, you have to
tell Nitin everything.
So he can defend you.
- Your bail application is rejected.
- What?
You're going to judicial custody
for fifteen days.
You know why?
Because they had proof
of everything.
And what did I have?
Tell him!
I had nothing!
Papa, get him.
He has to go to Taloja jail.
Come on.
I've done nothing.
- Come on, it's time.
- I've done nothing.
I've done nothing.
Come on.
Sir, thank you.
The cover, sir.
The media's swarming outside.
- Wear this.
- No, I don't want it.
- Hide your face from the media.
- No.
Let him be.
I'm innocent.
I didn't do anything.
Is your brother an idiot?
He is.
Don't stress too much.
It's just a fortnight.
Two weeks will go
in a jiffy.
The prison comes with a view.
Mountains, rivers...
Mother Nature!
Hair around the ears
must be closely trimmed.
Ears must be clearly visible
in the photographs.
- Name?
- Arvind Bhatia.
Left profile.
- Father's name?
- Naren Bhatia.
Left profile.
Section?
Sir, I am under trial.
My hearing is due next week.
- Go ahead. Next!
- Everyone here is under trial.
You're not special.
- Name?
- Samar Mehra.
- Father's name?
- Brigadier Mehra.
Is your father
the only Brigadier in the army?
- Say his full name.
- Pawanchand Mehra.
Rings, wallet, watch...
Remove everything
and put it on the table.
Clothes off. Footwear in hands.
- Got a prescription?
- I forgot.
Then forget the medicines as well.
What's that?
Waist belt for my lower back.
Take it off.
Remove it!
- How much money here?
- 5000.
Say 1000.
How much is it?
Say you have 1000 rupees.
How much does it have?
Man, why so confused?
It's your damn wallet!
Fingerprints.
Other hand.
Move.
Are you taking a shit?
Cough harder.
Go to the doctor.
Move.
Scram!
Come on.
Remove your underwear.
Didn't you hear me?
Strip!
And squat like a monkey.
Squat!
Cough.
These morons never understand.
Cough harder!
Now get up.
Go to the doctor.
Next!
Damn!
They even took your slippers.
Look around.
See anyone barefoot?
You look rich.
They'll find the smallest
of reasons to extort you.
Come on.
Come on, baby!
Wanna get laid?
Tonight won't be so bad,
we'll be in the other barrack.
Tomorrow, we'll be thrown
to these animals.
I can get you a safer barrack.
We have a fresh flower.
Don't let it dry.
You're that singer, right?
Rape-accused?
If anyone asks, say you're in
for Section 302, murder.
Or they'll eat you alive.
Where do you think you're going?
Move aside.
Don't sit on my leg.
I'm hungry as hell!
Want a mouthful
or a fistful?
Let us know, faggot!
We'll make sure you're well-fed.
The new ones are always hungry.
And we can barely digest it.
Hey, Chhotu.
Why are you staring?
Want to s**k my c**k?
D***head.
Sit down.
Hey! Chill out.
Want a safe barrack?
I can do it.
What will it take?
Money.
I don't have any.
How about your a** then?
Motherf*****g,
do I look like a fag?
I've already killed three.
Want to be my fourth?
Pipe down. I have
all your chargesheets.
What chargesheets?
You... robbed a shop.
Don't fall for his crap.
He's a f*****g snitch.
Hey, want a safer barrack?
Wanna stay alive?
Come on, wake up and pair up.
In twos.
Hey!
Squat like monkeys
in pairs of two.
Start counting in pairs.
One. Two. Three.
Four. Five. Six.
Eleven. Twelve. Thirteen.
Fourteen. Fifteen. Sixteen.
Seventeen. Eighteen.
Nineteen. Twenty.
Twenty-one. Twenty-two.
- Twenty-three. Twenty-four.
- UT number 1282.
Barrack 4, Circle 2.
UT number 1382.
Barrack 8, Circle 1.
UT number 1382?
What's up Lijo!
What's up, f****rs?
Get the pretty pigeon
in our coop.
Why me?
You're the only
smooth talker among us.
Bilal is going to
take him in.
Who?
That celebrity.
Bring him into our coop.
'So if I decide that
I don't want you to leave me,'
'then you can never leave me.'
Someone shut this geezer up.
Wake up and pair up!
Wake up the lizards!
Get up!
Start counting.
One. Two. Three.
Nine. Ten. Eleven. Twelve.
Twenty-three. Twenty-four.
Twenty-five. Twenty-six.
Twenty-seven.
f*****g morons!
Want to have my breakfast?
You think I'm a beggar?
Do I look like a beggar?
Do you f*****g know who I am?
I'm a bird.
Learn to deal with it.
Smoke the lizards
and time's a blur.
Bliss.
Where to?
Want to take a shit?
The elite toilet is taken.
So come later.
Hero.
Name?
Samar.
Samar what?
Mehra.
- Charge?
- 302.
Who did you kill?
That...
S-s-spit it out.
What?
Amnesia?
Forgot who he murdered.
Remember the infamous Delhi rape?
When the rapists reached
the prison...
Guess what the other inmates
did to them?
Fed them their own shit.
Forced their mouths open
and fed them shit.
Hungry? Are you?
Please sir, I'm innocent.
Motherf*****g liar.
Afraid to speak the truth?
Should have said 376.
Say you're here under Section 376!
Hey, where are you going?
Didn't you want to take a shit?
Come, let's take a shit.
Down with your pants.
Make way for His Highness.
Time for a royal dump.
Make way for him.
Down with them.
- Take your pants off, f****r!
- Aww, be kind.
Fast. Everyone here needs to shit.
Please remove your pants,
Mr. Mehra.
They even took away his footwear.
His privilege is a cage.
- Hey!
- Hello?
First time in prison?
Which section?
302!
'Why are you on a dating app?'
'You could get any girl.'
Samar.
Gayatri. Hi!
You have a British passport.
Why'd you want to live in Mumbai?
I eloped with my lover,
came here to get married.
And then?
Then he left me.
"Magic in your smile"
"Mischief in your stride"
"What is this curious feeling?"
"Are you the one I've been seeking?"
"All my heart's old habits"
"Why are they fading away?"
"In these little fleeting talks"
"It finds new ways to drift astray"
"Why does this feel so right?"
"My heart is singing in delight"
What are you most afraid of?
- Who are you scared of?
- Of myself.
Sometimes, I feel
I'm a really nice guy.
But at times, I feel sick...
Like I'm a monster.
Have a seat.
Sir, my name is Gayatri Anand.
'I want to file a case
against Samar Mehra.'
'UT Number 1382'
'Your bail hearing is
on the 23rd, at 2 PM.'
Here you go.
Saw the mountain view?
Look, no matter what,
don't pick up any
addictions in prison.
Remember that.
You're into bodybuilding, right?
Keep exercising!
Or else you'll get rusty.
It will all be fine.
Don't worry.
Drugs are no good.
They'll ruin you.
Yeah, tell me.
What?
Alright
Hey, turn back.
Turn back,
the hearing is over.
The hearing is over.
Let's go!
There they come!
- Careful!
Fuck off, moron!
You okay?
You should've eaten.
I saw what they did to you
in the toilet block.
This is how they bully us.
Like dogs.
What do you mean, us?
What they did to you is done
to us everyday.
By us, I mean we,
under Section 376.
Rape-accused.
I didn't rape anyone.
There was this woman.
I didn't know
she was married.
We hooked up
at a hotel a few times.
Her husband caught us,
and she framed me.
She claimed that
I blackmailed her...
into having sex.
Now she comes to court,
dressed like a demure bride.
The way she looks at me...
Do you...
Want to join our coop?
Coop?
Bilal, this is Samar.
How much worth of coupons
do you have with the cops?
1000.
1000?
Sit down.
Did you do it?
What?
Did you actually do it?
Was she your girlfriend?
Met her a few times.
Was it fun?
When women are really horny,
they just goes for it, bro.
This girl in my village...
What?
She'd screw anyone.
The scandal reached the village council.
Then?
Couple of the council men
gave her what she asked for.
What you sow is a cage.
What you reap is a cage.
It costs you your daily wage.
It's all a cage.
Country is a cage.
Society is a cage.
Tradition shoved up your ass,
it's all a cage.
"What you sow is a cage
What you reap is a cage"
"The daily grind
screwing your mind"
"It's all a cage"
"What you sow is a cage
What you reap is a cage"
"The daily grind
screwing your mind"
"It's all a cage"
"Country is a cage
Society is a cage"
"Faith and tradition
shoved up your ass,"
"It's all a cage"
"Girlfriends, wives
They're a cage"
"Phones, TV
It's all a cage"
"Love's a cage
Sex is a cage"
"Banks are a cage
Tax is a cage"
"Tax is a cage..."
"Sex is a cage."
"Home is a cage
Workplace is a cage"
"That house
you bought on mortgage"
"It's all a cage"
"Religion is a cage
Caste is a cage"
"All the wisdom
contained in books"
"It's all a cage"
"The votes they ask for
are a cage"
"The notes they hand out
"The game you played
The wager you made"
"The wounds you hide deep inside
It's all a cage"
"Motherhood's a cage
Fatherhood's a cage"
"The kids you birthed
are a cage"
"Caged outside
Caged inside"
"Trapped like goddamn monkeys"
"Monkeys in a cage"
"We're monkeys in a cage"
Do you really believe
everyone here is innocent?
If I don't, I'll lose
any little hope I have left.
No one here
seems innocent to me.
Not even me?
What happened?
- I hurt myself flossing.
- Show me.
There's a wound.
"What you sow is a cage
What you reap is a cage"
"The daily grind
screwing your mind"
"It's all a cage"
"Country is a cage
Society is a cage"
"Faith and tradition
shoved up your butt"
What's up?
It's always hard at first.
You're lucky at least
your family cares.
I haven't even seen my wife,
family in six years.
I don't even know
what my kid looks like.
What were you accused of?
I was a building security guard.
A girl got raped,
and murdered.
And the bloody cops framed me.
Claimed I was the one seen
in the security footage.
It was my bloody job
as a guard to do the rounds.
The victim's friend made
a statement against me.
Saying I'd lech at her.
Why wouldn't I lech?
Flaunting her rack
in skimpy clothes.
I'm a man after all.
Whoever screwed her
was one lucky b*****d.
Hey!
Why are you looking away?
Nothing.
Think you can judge me?
You think you're
the only innocent here?
Stop it.
Don't talk down to me
in English, a*****e!
Like that f*****g whore.
Always talking down to me.
Like I was an insect.
You b*****d
Leave him alone!
Motherf****r!
'Riot in Circle 1!'
'Everyone squat down
and pair up.'
'Pair up and squat down.'
Narcissism is a cage.
Take him away!
Pair up.
Motherf****r!
What are you doing here?
Bust all your balls.
a*****e!
Move!
Everyone must be in a pair.
When I tell you...
return to your cells.
What the fuck, man?
Always missing out on all the fun!
Fuckin shitting all the time.
f*****g idiots.
Guddu!
- You okay?
- Get him.
Yeah, I am okay.
Don't stare at them.
Lijo has asked for you.
Bilal won't like it,
there'll be trouble.
There will be bigger trouble
if he doesn't come right now.
Didn't you hear?
Sit.
Are you married?
No.
Why?
Just didn't want to.
Girlfriend?
- The one who filed the case?
- No.
Another one.
How much do you have
in coupons?
One thousand.
That's all?
You want to stay in this coop,
or go back to that bully?
Stay here.
Didn't hear you.
1000 is not enough to be a
part of us.
It'll cost you 5000.
Can you arrange it?
I don't have that much money.
But I can speak to my sister.
Day after is Canteen Day.
What you can do is,
give me your sister's number.
I won't hit on her, you moron.
The canteen manager will call her,
and she can transfer the money
to him directly.
'UT number 1382.
Come to the meeting area.'
Brother.
Are you okay?
Are you eating properly?
Please don't cry.
I brought your clothes
and medicines.
1382.
How are Mom and Dad?
Do they know?
It's all over the news.
I didn't tell them anything
but they still found out.
Papa is okay,
but mom keeps crying.
I'll handle them.
Don't let them come here.
They can't see me like this.
No. They won't come, brother.
They won't come.
Trust me they won't.
I am trying, brother.
- Khushi didn't come?
- She can't, brother.
Only family and lawyer.
Hey, time's up.
But sir,
the meeting just began.
To extend it, your sister has
to pay 5000 rupees.
No, this is not allowed.
- Please sir, we just got here.
- Give us five minutes.
Sir, we'll pay up!
Wait, I'll just go see.
Get me out of here!
I can't stay locked up
with these animals.
They'll kill me.
You have to get me
out of here.
Yeah, we are trying.
We are!
Please don't cry.
Samar, the next hearing
has been pushed.
Why? What happened?
Nothing to worry about.
It's regular procedure.
They just want to frustrate us.
I've lodged a complaint.
And there's good news:
I'm meeting the judge tomorrow.
I got my father to call him.
They were batchmates.
He's trying his best.
If they're batchmates,
why is it taking so long?
Can't he just get me out?
He's a judge,
not a fixer.
He's agreed to meet us.
It's a big deal.
Let him hear us out.
Just be patient.
- Brother.
- What?
What...
Please be strong.
I'm trying.
Yes, you're trying.
Suhani, I'm trying.
I know you are.
I know you are also trying.
No, no, please Samar.
I don't know how I got here.
I don't know what I am.
One more week, Samar.
We'll get the hearing soon.
They produce new evidence
at every hearing.
I'm just trying my best
to gather what I can.
I don't want anything.
Just get me out of here.
- It's a rape case, Samar.
- Stop saying that!
Stop. I can't hear that word - rape!
I can't hear that word - rape!
I'm a murderer.
I'm not a rapist.
- but we have to convince the judge.
- I'm a murderer. I'm a murderer.
Brother!
Next. Keep moving.
Some of that please.
Don't be clever with him.
The uniforms spike the chutney
with sedatives.
So one can sleep long hours.
As a side effect,
your cock won't crow.
If you agree to apologise,
I'll bring him back.
I'll talk to him.
Every coop has rules.
We stick together.
Eat, drink, sleep, shit together.
No contact with other coops.
We don't even greet them.
Behind you, that's Mello.
Only by name!
Flew down from Nigeria
with cocaine up his ass.
And here...
That's John.
Section 392. Robbery.
Guddu.
Same, 392.
And him...
Chhotu.
302.
Falsely accused of
murdering his father.
False my foot!
He literally boasts
about killing his father.
Yeah, why don't you invite
the warden for a feast
and then announce it
to the whole goddamn prison!
- Warden! He did kill his father.
- Shut up, you d**khead.
Why are they laughing so much?
He has murdered!
Fuck it, let milk and mocha
make a shake out of him. He'll learn.
And this English rose... Shining.
Bro, it's Shane.
Yes! Shane!
He wears a red band
because he's broken out
of prison nine times.
Every time he's brought back
opium up his ass.
And you?
Me?
Me? I'm the whole damn
Indian Penal Code!
Those f****rs have every charge
in the book on me.
Except yours.
Sit down, a*****e.
She's our sister-in-law.
Heard of the gangster Babu?
He's over there,
in the high security cell.
His girlfriend
visits every night,
with a bottle of booze.
Earlier, they had the eunuchs
in here, in a separate barrack.
Later, they moved them to
the HIV and Tuberculosis cell.
Otherwise like Babu,
our needs would be met too.
'Go call the cops!
f*****g a*****e!'
'Fuck you and your slags,
you f*****g a*****e!'
'I'll destroy you.'
'You wait and watch!'
'You fuck with me,
I'll fuckin have you, bitch!'
I got you snacks too!
They're selling a
40 rupee cola for 200.
Like they own this shit.
Here, take your swig.
Slow down, don't gulp it all.
Two sips for everyone.
I just took one sip,
a*****e!
You don't sip, you gulp!
Thank you.
I'll give you something to sip.
B****** said he only has
coupons worth a thousand.
Look at those mix-breeds
feasting off him.
They slaughtered that pretty pigeon
and made Biryani out of him.
Who asked you to s-s-slap him?
Is she an astrologer?
She's a healer.
Meaning?
She heals people.
Heels? She sticks them
up your bum?
Healing is like black magic.
Oh, I see!
Like those pastors
back home who touch people
and shock them
with their holy current.
Touch me, I'll show you.
What the hell did you do?
Did someone flick his balls?
Looks like a "sittud"
crawled up his ass!
My dad once got me a toy monkey.
It danced just like that
when you turned its key.
What's a "sittud"?
It's a tiny eel.
Vibrates like that in the pond.
How was she?
She was what she was.
What do you mean?
She could move a rock
by staring at it...
That's what she said.
Ooh, a sorceress!
My wife also would scare me
with those spooky stares.
One day, I got drunk
and knocked it out of her!
You're making a mistake, Samar.
I don't want to talk to you.
You don't know that Lijo.
He's just squeezing you.
He's keeping you in his coop
only for your money.
Once he's bled you dry,
he'll dump you.
Then no one will want you.
I'm not supposed to talk to you.
Don't talk, just listen.
I spoke to Bilal,
he's agreed to apologise.
He wants you back.
You can say sorry, too.
I don't want to go back.
Why?
Are you afraid?
Of everyone judging you as
a branded rapist in our coop?
You know that old man's story?
The one who howls in despair,
every night.
The old man is mute.
Can't speak.
No one remembers how long
he's been here.
No visitors,
no hearings, no conviction, ever.
His daughter-in-law didn't
want him living with them.
Didn't want to nurse
a sick old man.
The husband refused to
get rid of his father.
So the daughter-in-law
accused him of molesting her...
when her husband was at work.
Capital punishment is more dignified
than being accused of rape.
So one gives a shit
whether we did it or not.
Once you're stamped with Section 376,
you're a rapist for life.
Hey... what are you looking at?
Trying to figure what
makes them so indestructible...
The atomic bomb they dropped
decimated Hiroshima.
Trees, plants, humans,
buildings, all decimated except them.
They survived nuclear radiation.
Spoke to your family?
Or your girlfriend?
Wrote her two letters.
No response.
Are you really that stupid?
You think you'll put her name
and address on the letter
and they'll deliver it to her?
Haven't you understood the game yet?
Everything comes at a price here.
Prisons are the world's
most expensive hotels.
Get that?
That's the only way it works.
Write whatever you feel,
and give that to me,
along with her phone number.
The uniforms will WhatsApp her.
They charge 10,000 per letter.
And if you want her response,
that'll be 10 grand extra.
Madam, this UT-1382,
for him.
Delayed again?
- For how long?
- Another week.
Another week!
I'm sorry Samar.
We're trying our level best...
I know. You're trying.
You're trying your best!
Your father spoke to the judge,
what happened there?
What happened?
Bhai...
It's not Nitin's fault.
Gayatri's lawyer asked for more time.
Suhani, fuck it.
Just send me 10,000 rupees
more in the same account.
But we just gave you 8000!
I know.
Time's over. Leave now!
Just a minute.
I need that ten thousand.
Everything costs money, here.
Sir, you can't do this.
Please, hear me out.
10,000!
But why? This is illegal!
I'll complain to the Inspector General.
How can you ask for money?
'I'll grab your throat,
choke you, while I...'
'Fuck your brains out.'
'Would you like that?'
Will you really choke me?
They say it gives you
a powerful orgasm.
I...
It won't kill me?
Are you crazy?
I'm not a serial killer.
I'll just stop your breath
for a second...
Okay, do it.
Forget it.
Wanna smoke?
When was the last time you
cut yourself?
Before I moved to Bombay.
Living at home
was unbearable.
Mom and Dad would
both get pissed drunk,
And then: "Fuck you!"
"Motherf****r!"
"Get out!"
I hated every minute
of my childhood.
You know, I don't understand
why people get married.
Your parents?
They're happily married.
Then why are you like this?
Like what?
Why are you on a dating app?
You could get any girl you want.
You think so?
What?
You're so beautiful!
You know you're beautiful,
don't you?
In school, the other kids said
I'd be a hero one day.
Then?
I'm still waiting for that day.
I'll make you a hero.
You'll make me a hero?
Yes.
How?
The energy in your house...
It's not good.
Let me fix that for you,
and then see...
You'll make the front page
of every tabloid!
I can feel it.
You think you can
make me a star?
I have superpowers.
As a child,
I would stare at a rock,
and...
It would move.
If I really make up my mind,
I can alter
your fate and future.
So if I decide,
that I don't want you
to ever leave me...
I'm kidding!
But of course,
I can't force you.
You can leave me
if you want to.
Do you want to leave me?
We've only just met.
But don't you want to
see me again?
I do.
And again?
Yeah.
You know...
I have a meeting in the morning.
I need to sleep.
Yeah, let's sleep.
Meeting is important.
I prefer sleeping alone.
Love you.
Bye.
- Is he home?
- Yes.
I cooked especially for you.
Homemade yoghurt.
Sir isn't home today.
I know.
You don't look 35.
You don't look 50.
So, what do we do?
I was just saying.
Didn't you see my age
before you swiped?
I just saw your photo
and I swiped.
Oh. You were expecting
someone younger?
No, no, I was expecting you only.
I always check the age of the guy.
Men's brains don't develop
entirely till they're about 50.
Or is it that
I have daddy issues?
"I have placed the crystals.
Now energies will align."
All okay? Ex?
Long story?
Fun story!
Tell me.
That girl... they discovered
another boyfriend of hers,
and he's ready to
testify against her.
Congratulations!
Thank you, Samar.
This time, even if she
acts like a virgin in court,
the judge won't buy it.
All the best to you, too.
When is your hearing?
Pushed by another week.
Again?
You need to talk
to your lawyer.
All this delay,
it's not good.
Third time, right?
Speak to your lawyer.
These cops are messing around,
I can guarantee that.
Besides, everyone here...
What?
If dates keep getting pushed,
eventually everyone here too
gets convinced you're guilty.
How will you survive
if you're stuck here for longer?
Lijo will s**k you dry.
How long will you
let them leech off you?
Think about it.
I can still talk to Bilal
if you like.
No.
I don't want to
join his coop.
Okay, then...
keep this.
- Are you crazy? I don't want it.
- Trust me, you'll need it! Keep it.
Don't you get it?
I don't want to talk to you!
Go away!
Guddu!
Guddu, look!
Guddu, please.
Don't tell Lijo, please.
Get lost!
What happened?
He was talking to that guy
from the rapist gang.
Whispering to each other.
That's the one.
Motherf****r!
Why don't you go fuck
within your own coop?
f*****g rapists, all of them.
What's your problem?
Did I fuck your mother?
Get your mother f****d
by your own coop!
You're experienced.
Watch your tongue.
Worry about yourself!
What? Want to s**k my d**k?
Or you only s**k Daddy Lijo?
Son of a f*****g pimp!
What did I tell you?
Lijo, brother...
If you like hanging with
those rapists, go ahead.
I don't give a fuck.
But if you're in my gang,
and I catch you talking
to Bilal's men again...
You still owe 10,000.
Next week is Canteen Day.
I want it before then.
She's the girl, right?
Mom...
Please don't stare.
Sir, this is fresh evidence.
The prosecution has introduced it
last minute, like every time.
We haven't even had a chance
to verify it.
You verified the photos and messages
your client sent the victim, right?
Yes, sir.
You sure?
I'll just read it out.
"How're you doing, babe?"
"Hey babes, would like
to see you nake-"
Yes sir, I've read them.
Your Honour,
we also have statements
from the spa owner
and the masseuse,
who say they gave
my client and the accused
a couple's massage.
Is that even legal here?
Yes, sir.
It's quite normal in many spas.
- Normal, really?
- Many couples opt for it.
You earlier said your client
was intimate with the victim only once.
Now there's this
couple's massage too...
Sir, this is a massage.
This is a...
This is what? Keep quiet.
Include Exhibit 18
in the proceedings.
This contradicts the defence's claim,
that the client met the victim
only once.
Your Honour, please.
Give us time to verify this document
and cross-examine the witness.
That's it, please, sir.
Your client is a danger to society.
- How does society come into this?
- He's a threat to our daughters!
- Do you understand?
- What are you saying, sir!
And you want me to give him bail.
Set him free? No.
Look at the evidence,
read the messages.
All that filth!
- Go through them carefully...
- I have read them-
Sir, it's a personal choice.
No, he is nothing
but sexually repressed.
Sir, our entire country
is sexually repressed.
Don't get our country into this!
This is about the film industry
your client belongs to...
- He hasn't had work for years--
- Where it's all sex, drugs--
- Couch potato...
- Casting couch.
That's all that happens!
Sir, what does the casting couch
have to do with this?
If this happened in another country,
he'd be stoned to death.
Our country has values.
We have respect.
Do you understand?
No bail.
Thank you, Your Honour.
Uncle, please.
I didn't expect this from you.
"Our country is repressed."
My dear, can I speak to you
for a minute?
Ma'am, that's not allowed.
- Mom, please, this isn't allowed.
- Please, just two minutes.
What's going on here?
- Speak to Inspector Deore...
- Leave my client alone!
- Now!
- Mom, let's go.
You know influencing the victim
is against the law, right?
- Come with me.
- Mom, please let's go.
She tricked me.
She gifted me that coupon.
When I got there,
I realised it was a couples' spa
and she was already there.
You should've told us this.
If she still has the coupon,
that means she had planned it.
Samar, I've told you
a thousand times,
you have to
tell Nitin everything.
If you don't,
how will he help?
He's really trying.
Is he?
No, he's not trying.
He doesn't have any idea
what we are going through.
You think this is
easy for us?
You have no idea what Mom,
Dad and I are going through.
You have no f*****g idea!
Whether it's home
or the office,
The media swarms outside,
all day long!
I can barely step out!
All our phones
are ringing nonstop.
Because everyone wants to know
whether you raped her or not.
Everyone asks me:
"As a woman, how can you
support your brother?"
Why shouldn't I?
What should I do?
Leave you to die?
You have no f*****g idea,
Bhai...
You have no idea!
Samar, try to understand.
The prosecution will
keep producing new evidence,
and the hearing will
keep getting pushed.
The 10,000 rupees.
I need it.
Is he even hearing
what we're saying?
What else do you want?
Tell me.
Butter chicken
from a five-star?
MS Dhoni's autograph?
What else do you want?
- Please Suhani, don't shout.
- Tell me!
I need ten thousand rupees, Suhani.
I'm sorry but I need it.
Samar, listen to me.
I need the-
Samar, if there's anything,
now is the time to say it.
I have nothing else to say!
Nothing!
I have to get those ten thousand rupees.
I need the money.
Listen Samar,
we need information.
Every small detail
you can remember.
It cannot go on like it is.
Can you get this?
Sometimes, I feel like
I'm committing a crime
by supporting you.
Brother,
you're not getting it.
Please help us!
I need...
Ten thousand rupees.
I can't do this.
I'm sorry.
You are not sorry.
You are not sorry, Samar!
You are not sorry!
You have no f*****g idea!
- You want to stay here forever?
- I don't want to stay here!
I really need the money.
Why else would I ask for it?
I know what you all are
going through!
- Which is why we are here to help...
- I didn't do anything!
I need the money, please!
Okay.
You'll get the money.
But please help us out.
We'll arrange the money.
Ok?
Samar, what are you doing?
Go to sleep, a*****e!
Samar!
Did you fall down jerking off,
or did someone push you?
Shut up and sleep!
Wanna die?
Creating a goddamn racket
in the middle of the night.
I'm not doing anything.
They are.
I keep swatting them,
but they just don't die.
What the hell
are you blabbering?
Have you lost it?
They follow me everywhere.
Don't you get it?
She told me,
she has powers.
Like X-Men.
Samar, wake up.
You're overthinking, boy.
It will drive you crazy.
This place is such...
Can't tell if
it's day or night.
A 20-person barrack
has 100 inmates.
And after all the hell
we endure,
we have to survive.
Because they don't
allow us to die.
To survive this ordeal,
we have to embrace our fate.
We have to accept it.
Or this place will
drive you nuts.
You can either make peace
with your fate,
or you can change it.
I have people on the outside.
I can send some guys...
To the girl's house.
But it will cost money.
Can you pay?
Did you call Bilal?
What the fuck happened here?
Look.
How did this...?
He's dead!
Did anyone do it to him?
Move.
He killed himself.
- Move.
Which motherf****r
did this to him?
Did anyone threaten him?
Pick him up.
Move, make way.
Aatish.
Look at the blood.
Why did he do it?
You were
my only ray of light!
Aatish.
His bail got rejected.
The other guy that girl slept with
was supposed to testify.
He turned hostile.
Twenty-one. Twenty-two.
Twenty-three. Twenty-four.
Twenty-five. Twenty-six. Twenty-seven.
Twenty-eight. Twenty-nine. Thirty.
Thirty-two. Thirty-three. Thirty-four.
I prefer to sleep alone.
It's the first time.
I sleep alone too, actually.
Bye.
M-U-S-C-L-E!
Take the call.
- Khushi madam?
- Yes.
Khushi ma'am, your coffee.
Don't call me "ma'am".
Just Khushi, please.
You're older than me!
Yes ma'am.
Khushi!
- Your turn.
- One second.
Who is it?
This annoying producer...
Getting on my nerves.
Then block him.
Samar!
- Samar, please. Please talk to me.
- Stay away from me.
- I said stay away from me.
- Please unblock me.
- Watchman!
- Samar, please. Just once...
Don't let this crazy woman
hover around here.
She's a nuisance.
Fuck you!
Don't fuck with me!
Give me your phone!
- Madam...!
Hello?
Is this because I was scared
to let you choke me-
Samar, don't disconnect,
please!
Listen, stop calling me.
Samar, you don't understand!
Listen, let me finish
your house, please!
If I see you again,
I will call the cops.
Cops? You'll call the f*****g cops?
Go ahead, motherf****r!
Go call the cops!
F****g a*****e!
F*** you and all your slags.
You f*****g a*****e!
I will destroy you.
You wait and watch!
You f*** with me,
I will f*****g have you, b***h!
Stick to what
you've been told.
Have a seat.
We want to file an FIR.
What's the complaint?
Rape.
Come.
'Dear Samar,'
'I don't know
what to say...'
'or how to write to you.'
'I've trying to do this
for a while...'
'and I'm still struggling.'
'So, I'll keep this short.'
'I can't remember the last time'
'I felt such opposing emotions
for someone.'
'I get angry.
I get frustrated and lash out'
'Sometimes at you,
sometimes at myself.'
'I'm so angry inside,'
'and I don't even know
at who.'
'I've tried very hard
not to think of you,'
'but I failed.'
'Last night, I sat up watching
all episodes of your shitty show.'
'And I realized I can't see you
the way I used to anymore.'
'Remember when I told you,
to get out of your bubble?'
'Now it feels like I'm in one.'
'I don't know
who to believe anymore.'
'I can't do this anymore,
Samar.'
'Take this as my last message.'
'I hope you
find your peace.'
'Khushi.'
Hey!
Beauty queen.
Your hero is trying
to get out on bail.
If no harm is done to you,
he'll get out easily.
Understood?
So do something!
Get someone to threaten you
with an acid attack.
Acid?
Bloody dumbass...
Dude...
Withdraw the case, or it'll
be real acid next time!
'UT number 1382, 2255, 813.'
'Your bail hearing is at 12 noon today.'
'Your bail hearing
is at noon today.'
'UT number 1382, 2255, 813.'
- Your hearing's today, wont you go?
'Your bail hearing
is at noon today.'
It's your hearing today.
Wait.
What now?
UT 1382. His hearing is cancelled.
Take him out.
What happened?
The girl was attacked.
She was threatened with acid
to withdraw the case.
Come on out.
I didn't get any call.
The Superintendent got a call.
Deore Sir called?
Where's Lijo?
What happened?
Where is he?
- What happened?
- He's taking a dump.
What happened to him?
It did not work out. So...
He is acting different...
You did it.
What?
You did it, right?
You sent your men
to throw acid on her.
Have you lost your mind?
I gave you an option.
You didn't take it.
So why the fuck would I do
it for free?
Then who did?
Who the fuck did it?
Who else would do it?
Get that motherf****r!
Break his bones!
Hey, stop!
Move.
A*****e!
f*****g traitor...
C***!
Stop!
I'm a driver,
I didn't do anything!
I swear,
I'm just a driver!
'Dear Khushi,'
'You always told me:
"Come out of your bubble"'
'And I'd get angry.'
'My sister would
say this, too.'
'I can't remember the last time'
'I wrote a letter to someone.'
'Perhaps to my grandfather.'
'He was unwell at the time.'
'He never read it..'
'He passed away before
he received it.'
'Ever since...'
'I have a bad feeling
about writing letters.'
'This is a prison
for undertrials. '
'Everyone is accused,
and everyone claims innocence.'
'But understanding what innocence
truly means, takes time.'
'Each one believes that
their acts were justified.'
'Prison screws us up
in various ways.'
'But it also teaches us
the value of little things.'
'Like how valuable the wall is
to rest our backs.'
'Prisons have no mirrors...'
'because anyone can break the glass
and use shards as weapons.'
'People don't get to see
their own faces for years.'
'Inmates forget
what they looked like.'
'And we don't know
night from day.'
'They keep the lights on
all the time.'
'To make sure
we don't dream of hope.'
'Those who've been here
for years'
'say even our dreams
lose color after a while.'
'We've all become ghosts here.'
'Ghosts who terrify no one else,
but ourselves.'
'I didn't handle this situation
with Gayatri well.'
'I got scared.'
'I never knew I drove her
to that point.'
'If ever I've hurt you,
even by mistake...'
'then I'm sorry.'
'I finally understand...'
'We're all but monkeys
in our own circus.'
The country is a cage.
Society is a cage.
Religion, tradition,
shoved up your ass...
It's all a cage.
What's the charge?
302.
You're Samar, right?
Samar Mehra.
I read about you.
You did?
What do you think?
Did I do it?
Or not?
"We are all accused,
accused, accused"
"For one who messed up,
four got screwed"
"Innocent and guilty,
all in this together"
"We are all condemned,
condemned, condemned"
"We are all accused,
accused, accused"
"For one who messed up,
four got screwed"
"Innocent and guilty,
all in this together"
"We are all condemned,
condemned, condemned"
"We are all accused"
"Welcome to prison,
the kingdom of dry bread"
"Stained clothes, iron plates
food straight from hell"
"Welcome to prison,
to the handsome rapists"
"They're the first to get f****d
and they're always f****d dry"
"Welcome to the slammer,
to the insane asylum"
"Everything stinks, everyone sweats
everything s**ks, everyone stinks"
"Blows are fired,
war declared"
"A bowl, a spoon
are enough to stab you"
"It's not crime and punishment,
It's drugs and medication"
"We smoke the lizard
Kill the foxes"
"Itching to fight
No room to turn"
"Everyone's on an equal footing
when it comes to getting screwed"
"Welcome to the slack,
No money, no bail"
"Your release,
you stick it up your butt"
"Here, it's glory to the tiger
and death to the sheep"
"A moment of weakness
And you're getting f****d deep"
"We are all accused,
accused, accused"
"For one who messed up,
four got screwed"
"Innocent and guilty,
all in this together"
"We are all condemned,
condemned, condemned"
"We are all accused,
accused, accused"
"For one who messed up,
four got screwed"
"Innocent and guilty,
all in this together"
"We are all condemned,
condemned, condemned"
"We are all accused"
"Block number one:
Assault and battery"
"Fans of fighting,
marave, and brawling"
"Block number two:
Attempted murder"
"Those who start the work
but don't finish it"
"Block number three:
Intentional homicide"
"They sleep in prison
and their victims, six feet under"
"In the other blocks,
thieves, shooters, rapists"
"Thugs and scum
of all colors"
"Criminals"
"Petty-time criminals"
"On the run"
"Exiled thugs"
"7-star"
"Five grand"
"Here, everything smells of piss,
everything smells rancid"
"We are all accused,
accused, accused"
"For one who messed up,
four got screwed"
"Innocent and guilty,
all in this together"
"We are all condemned,
condemned, condemned"
"We are all accused,
accused, accused"
"For one who messed up,
four got screwed"
"Innocent and guilty,
all in this together"
"We are all condemned,
condemned, condemned"
"We are all accused"
"Welcome to the detention center"
"From the outside,
it looks like a prison"
"Inside, it's more expensive
than at a 7-star hotel"
"5,000 rupees for biryani"
"500 rupees per packet of biscuits"
"Don't get involved,
prison is unforgiving"
"So if I have one piece of advice:
behave yourself."